<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PIT tags on Down in the Holler</title>
    <link>/tags/pit-tags/</link>
    <description>Recent content in PIT tags on Down in the Holler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/pit-tags/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ontogeny of Southern Brook Lamprey (*Ichthyomyzon gagei*) with emphasis on abundance, distribution, and morphology in a small watershed</title>
      <link>/post/ontogeny-of-southern-brook-lamprey/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/ontogeny-of-southern-brook-lamprey/</guid>
      <description>Southern Brook Lamprey, Ichthyomyzon gagei, is a primitive, non-parasitic filter feeder that lives in sandy streams in the Southeastern United States. They experience three life stages: (1) ammocoete, (2) metamorphosis, and (3) adult. This study aims to assess the presence of Southern Brook Lamprey at nine sites within a small watershed, Panther Creek, on the Tombigbee National Forest just south of Starkville, Mississippi.
This browser does not support PDFs. Please download the PDF to view it: Download PDF.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Southeastern Fishes Council 44th (2018) Annual Meeting Presentation</title>
      <link>/post/2018-11-14-sfc-lamprey-pres/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2018-11-14-sfc-lamprey-pres/</guid>
      <description>This browser does not support PDFs. Please download the PDF to view it: Download PDF.
 
You can download the Microsoft Power Point version of this presentation from ResearchGate (link).
Also, don&amp;rsquo;t forget to follow the Southern Brook Lamprey project log on ResearchGate (link).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Assessing Viability of Passive Integrated Transponder (PIT) Tags for Ecological Studies of Lamprey Ammocoetes</title>
      <link>/post/2018-10-05-afs2018-lamprey/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2018-10-05-afs2018-lamprey/</guid>
      <description>Passive integrated transponder (PIT) tags are widely used to study movement and habitat preferences in large-bodied fish species. However, relatively large tag sizes have traditionally limited their suitability for small-bodied fishes. Technological advances have recently led to the production of smaller PIT tags (8.0 x 1.4 mm) that may prove useful to the study of small-bodied fish species, particularly those of conservation importance. Southern Brook Lamprey (Ichthyomyzon gagei) are small-bodied, filiform fish.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>