<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>travel on Caleb A. Aldridge</title>
    <link>/tags/travel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in travel on Caleb A. Aldridge</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2020, C.A. Aldridge; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/travel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Yellowstone Family Trip, Part I</title>
      <link>/post/2018-07-04-ysft-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2018-07-04-ysft-i/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re going on a trip&amp;hellip; &amp;hellip;in our favorite rocket ship ♪ ♫ Our rocket ship happens to be the same RAM 1500 we took on our trip the the Grand Canyon back in 2016 (link to that trip). What&amp;rsquo;s more exciting is that my aunt, Matilda, will be on this trip! I think she was a little envious of the experiences we shared on the trip prior and wasn&amp;rsquo;t going to let the opportunity pass her by.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grandparents to the Grand Canyon, Part V</title>
      <link>/post/2018-03-27-gp2gc-v/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2018-03-27-gp2gc-v/</guid>
      <description>Mesa Verde So my granddad (Poppa) has well-rounded interests and when two or more of those interest can be sparked by a single place or topic he&amp;rsquo;s a very perky fellow. The cultural and natural significance of Mesa Verde NP was such that we all were perked up. (More to come on this).
Traveling Back The drive home wasn&amp;rsquo;t too eventful, especially in light of what we had just experienced.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grandparents to the Grand Canyon, Part IV</title>
      <link>/post/2018-03-08-gp2gc-iv/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2018-03-08-gp2gc-iv/</guid>
      <description>Fractals I remember the first time I ever learned of a fractal. There was this screensaver on the old Windows &amp;lsquo;95 OS that was either a maze of with the walls a fractals or it morphed into a continuous fractal shape&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m not certain. I do remember that I could watch it for a few minutes&amp;mdash;which is an eternity when you are a first grader. I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure it was the screensaver in the clip below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grandparents to the Grand Canyon, Part III</title>
      <link>/post/2018-02-21-gp2gc-iii/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2018-02-21-gp2gc-iii/</guid>
      <description>Lee&amp;rsquo;s Ferry and Vermilion Cliffs National Monument (red cliffs) At the end of Part II in this series we had just been floored by the majesty of the Grand Canyon. From the South Rim Visitors Center we were making our way west on HWY-89; our last stop was the Desert Watchtower. We were now driving towards Page, AZ, but would head west on HWY-89A before reaching the Glen Canyon Dam and Lake Powell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grandparents to the Grand Canyon, Part II</title>
      <link>/post/2018-02-14-gp2gc-ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2018-02-14-gp2gc-ii/</guid>
      <description>Get some sleep In Part I of this series I gave a briefing on travel plans of getting my paternal grandparents to the Grand Canyon and beyond. When I left off, we had just arrived at our hotel the evening before we were to visit GCNP.
&amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip;[E]veryone was buzzing with excitement&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; and for different reasons. On this trip had come myself, my paternal grandparents (aka, Nana and Poppa), my Mom (Amy), Dad (Robert), and brother (David), and an uncle-in-law (Uncle Bryan) and first cousin (Cade).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grandparents to the Grand Canyon, Part I</title>
      <link>/post/2018-02-07-gp2gc-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2018-02-07-gp2gc-i/</guid>
      <description>Setting the stage(coach)  Quick note: This is the first in a short series about a trip I and family members took in July&amp;ndash;August of 2016. It may be a little longer and sappier than some are willing to endure, and I&amp;rsquo;m not that captivating of a writer. So if you&amp;rsquo;d like to skip to the photographs of our trip click here. After all, &amp;ldquo;One picture [is] worth ten thousand words&amp;rdquo; (Fred R.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>