<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Down in the Holler</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Down in the Holler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>New blog post on Colvin Lab website</title>
      <link>/post/2019-03-25-colvin-lab-website-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2019-03-25-colvin-lab-website-post/</guid>
      <description>The second half to the &amp;lsquo;Design and Decisions&amp;rsquo; posts. I authored a blog post for our lab website. Check it out here: https://mcolvin.github.io/2019-03-22-aldridge-blog-post/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge Discovery &amp; Decision Analysis in Managing US Inland Fisheries</title>
      <link>/post/2019-03-07-phd-proposal-pres/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2019-03-07-phd-proposal-pres/</guid>
      <description>I recently presented on my proposed dissertation research. I&amp;rsquo;m sure this will evolve as time goes by&amp;mdash;this is the launching pad.
This browser does not support PDFs. Please download the PDF to view it: Download PDF.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>45th Annual Meeting of the Mississippi Chapter of the American Fisheries Society</title>
      <link>/post/2019-02-21-msafs-poster/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2019-02-21-msafs-poster/</guid>
      <description>Fish length and age are common measurements collected by fisheries agencies. Together with catch per unit, agencies can assess important population parameters such as growth, mortality, and recruitment. But estimating age of individual fish is costly (e.g., time, fish mortality), and age structure is typically estimated from a subsample and expanded to whole sample. Expanding and estimating age structure of the sample is done using a probability matrix of age and length-class to partition individuals of the complete sample (age-length key [ALK]).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ontogeny of Southern Brook Lamprey, Ichthyomyzon gagei, with emphasis on abundance, distribution, and morphology in a small watershed</title>
      <link>/post/2019-02-26-msafs-lamprey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2019-02-26-msafs-lamprey/</guid>
      <description>A member of the Southern Brook Lamprey Research Group has been actively tracking the number and location of captured individuals. She has also been diligent in taking careful total length measures and classifying individuals into life-stages based on physical characteristics. Bayley was able to share her research with the SBLRG and with our minor contributions presented the slides below at the 45th Mississippi AFS meeting.
Abstract. The ecology of many non-game fish species is understudied, thus little information is known about the life-history and population structure of diverse fishes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New blog post on Colvin Lab website</title>
      <link>/post/2019-01-25-colvin-lab-website-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2019-01-25-colvin-lab-website-post/</guid>
      <description>I wrote that I authored a blog post for our lab website. It went live today! Check it out here: https://mcolvin.github.io/2019-01-25-aldridge/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Southeastern Fishes Council 44th (2018) Annual Meeting Presentation</title>
      <link>/post/2018-11-14-sfc-lamprey-pres/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2018-11-14-sfc-lamprey-pres/</guid>
      <description>This browser does not support PDFs. Please download the PDF to view it: Download PDF.
 
You can download the Microsoft Power Point version of this presentation from ResearchGate (link).
Also, don&amp;rsquo;t forget to follow the Southern Brook Lamprey project log on ResearchGate (link).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Assessing Viability of Passive Integrated Transponder (PIT) Tags for Ecological Studies of Lamprey Ammocoetes</title>
      <link>/post/2018-10-05-afs2018-lamprey/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2018-10-05-afs2018-lamprey/</guid>
      <description>Passive integrated transponder (PIT) tags are widely used to study movement and habitat preferences in large-bodied fish species. However, relatively large tag sizes have traditionally limited their suitability for small-bodied fishes. Technological advances have recently led to the production of smaller PIT tags (8.0 x 1.4 mm) that may prove useful to the study of small-bodied fish species, particularly those of conservation importance. Southern Brook Lamprey (Ichthyomyzon gagei) are small-bodied, filiform fish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yellowstone Family Trip, Part I</title>
      <link>/post/2018-07-04-ysft-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2018-07-04-ysft-i/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re going on a trip&amp;hellip; &amp;hellip;in our favorite rocket ship ♪ ♫ Our rocket ship happens to be the same RAM 1500 we took on our trip the the Grand Canyon back in 2016 (link to that trip). What&amp;rsquo;s more exciting is that my aunt, Matilda, will be on this trip! I think she was a little envious of the experiences we shared on the trip prior and wasn&amp;rsquo;t going to let the opportunity pass her by.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grandparents to the Grand Canyon, Part V</title>
      <link>/post/2018-03-27-gp2gc-v/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2018-03-27-gp2gc-v/</guid>
      <description>Mesa Verde So my granddad (Poppa) has well-rounded interests and when two or more of those interest can be sparked by a single place or topic he&amp;rsquo;s a very perky fellow. The cultural and natural significance of Mesa Verde NP was such that we all were perked up. (More to come on this).
Traveling Back The drive home wasn&amp;rsquo;t too eventful, especially in light of what we had just experienced.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grandparents to the Grand Canyon, Part IV</title>
      <link>/post/2018-03-08-gp2gc-iv/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2018-03-08-gp2gc-iv/</guid>
      <description>Fractals I remember the first time I ever learned of a fractal. There was this screensaver on the old Windows &amp;lsquo;95 OS that was either a maze of with the walls a fractals or it morphed into a continuous fractal shape&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m not certain. I do remember that I could watch it for a few minutes&amp;mdash;which is an eternity when you are a first grader. I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure it was the screensaver in the clip below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grandparents to the Grand Canyon, Part III</title>
      <link>/post/2018-02-21-gp2gc-iii/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2018-02-21-gp2gc-iii/</guid>
      <description>Lee&amp;rsquo;s Ferry and Vermilion Cliffs National Monument (red cliffs) At the end of Part II in this series we had just been floored by the majesty of the Grand Canyon. From the South Rim Visitors Center we were making our way west on HWY-89; our last stop was the Desert Watchtower. We were now driving towards Page, AZ, but would head west on HWY-89A before reaching the Glen Canyon Dam and Lake Powell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grandparents to the Grand Canyon, Part II</title>
      <link>/post/2018-02-14-gp2gc-ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2018-02-14-gp2gc-ii/</guid>
      <description>Get some sleep In Part I of this series I gave a briefing on travel plans of getting my paternal grandparents to the Grand Canyon and beyond. When I left off, we had just arrived at our hotel the evening before we were to visit GCNP.
&amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip;[E]veryone was buzzing with excitement&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; and for different reasons. On this trip had come myself, my paternal grandparents (aka, Nana and Poppa), my Mom (Amy), Dad (Robert), and brother (David), and an uncle-in-law (Uncle Bryan) and first cousin (Cade).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grandparents to the Grand Canyon, Part I</title>
      <link>/post/2018-02-07-gp2gc-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2018-02-07-gp2gc-i/</guid>
      <description>Setting the stage(coach)  Quick note: This is the first in a short series about a trip I and family members took in July&amp;ndash;August of 2016. It may be a little longer and sappier than some are willing to endure, and I&amp;rsquo;m not that captivating of a writer. So if you&amp;rsquo;d like to skip to the photographs of our trip click here. After all, &amp;ldquo;One picture [is] worth ten thousand words&amp;rdquo; (Fred R.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A preliminary investigation of Feral Hog impacts on water quality</title>
      <link>/post/2017-07-21-hog-water-quality-poster/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2017-07-21-hog-water-quality-poster/</guid>
      <description>This is a poster that Brent Chaney presented at a Miss. State Univ. undergraduate symposium in 2017. I worked with him on producing the graphs and analyzing the data to get at the questions he was asking.
This browser does not support PDFs. Please download the PDF to view it: Download PDF.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Masters thesis presentation -- The effect of road-crossings on stream-associated salamanders within Holly Springs National Forest</title>
      <link>/post/2017-04-29-masters-thesis-presentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2017-04-29-masters-thesis-presentation/</guid>
      <description>These are the slides from my Masters thesis presentation. The PowerPoint file of my presentation became corrupt just two nights before the presentation! It was a crazy shuffle, but I managed to get a skeleton presentation together and passed my thesis defense. Looking back, I could have been better prepared in preventing the file corruption and the presentation itself. It&amp;rsquo;s always good to keep track of where you&amp;rsquo;ve come from though.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrate from Jekyll</title>
      <link>/post/migrate-from-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2015 13:07:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/migrate-from-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>Move static content to static Jekyll has a rule that any directory not starting with _ will be copied as-is to the _site output. Hugo keeps all static content under static. You should therefore move it all there. With Jekyll, something that looked like
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ images/ logo.png  should become
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ static/ ▾ images/ logo.png  Additionally, you&amp;rsquo;ll want any files that should reside at the root (such as CNAME) to be moved to static.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go is for lovers</title>
      <link>/post/go-is-for-lovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2015 13:47:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/go-is-for-lovers/</guid>
      <description>Hugo uses the excellent go html/template library for its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of similarities in go templates.
This document is a brief primer on using go templates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo is for lovers</title>
      <link>/post/hugo-is-for-lovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2015 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/hugo-is-for-lovers/</guid>
      <description>Step 1. Install Hugo Goto hugo releases and download the appropriate version for your os and architecture.
Save it somewhere specific as we will be using it in the next step.
More complete instructions are available at installing hugo
Step 2. Build the Docs Hugo has its own example site which happens to also be the documentation site you are reading right now.
Follow the following steps:
 Clone the hugo repository Go into the repo Run hugo in server mode and build the docs Open your browser to http://localhost:1313  Corresponding pseudo commands:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a new theme</title>
      <link>/post/creating-a-new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2015 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/creating-a-new-theme/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>